{"transport":[{"level":"1","type":"transport","question":"I have wheels and go 'beep beep'! Little ones ride in me.","hints":[{"text":"👪 I take children to school."},{"text":"🛑 I usually stop at a yellow light."},{"text":"🚏 You wait for me at a specific place on the road."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Train","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"2","type":"transport","question":"I float on water and carry people or things across the sea.","hints":[{"text":"🌊 I need a large body of water."},{"text":"⚓️ I have an anchor to stay in one place."},{"text":"🚢 I am much bigger than a rowboat."}],"options":[{"label":"Boat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Train","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Car","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"3","type":"transport","question":"I fly high in the sky and take people to far away places.","hints":[{"text":"☁️ I fly above the clouds."},{"text":"💺 I have many seats for passengers."},{"text":"✈️ You need a ticket to ride me."}],"options":[{"label":"Helicopter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Rocket","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"4","type":"transport","question":"I go on tracks and carry many people. I can be very long.","hints":[{"text":"🛤️ I follow a specific path."},{"text":"🚊 I have lots of carriages."},{"text":"🚂 I often travel between cities."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Train","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Truck","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"5","type":"transport","question":"I have two wheels and you use your feet to move me.","hints":[{"text":"🦶 You need to pedal to make me go."},{"text":"🔔 I often have a bell."},{"text":"🚲 You can ride me in the park."}],"options":[{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bicycle","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Skateboard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"6","type":"transport","question":"I zoom through the air and can go to outer space!","hints":[{"text":"🚀 I use a lot of fuel to launch."},{"text":"👩‍🚀 Astronauts travel in me."},{"text":"🌌 I can travel to the moon."}],"options":[{"label":"Helicopter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rocket","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"7","type":"transport","question":"I'm like a car, but people pay to ride in me and I have a meter.","hints":[{"text":"🚦 You can wave me down on the street."},{"text":"🚕 I'm often yellow."},{"text":"📍 I take you where you want to go."}],"options":[{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Taxi","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Truck","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"8","type":"transport","question":"I am a vehicle that helps to put out fires.","hints":[{"text":"🚨 I have a siren."},{"text":"👨‍🚒 Firefighters ride in me."},{"text":"💧 I spray water."}],"options":[{"label":"Police Car","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ambulance","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Firetruck","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"9","type":"transport","question":"I am like a motorbike but I have three wheels.","hints":[{"text":"⚙️ I am good for carrying things."},{"text":"🇮🇳 I am popular in some countries."},{"text":"🛵 Sometimes I am called an auto-rickshaw."}],"options":[{"label":"Tuk-Tuk","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Scooter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Quad Bike","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"10","type":"transport","question":"I am a fast train that travels under cities.","hints":[{"text":"🚇 I use underground tunnels."},{"text":"🗺️ You can use me to travel quickly in a big city."},{"text":"🛤️ I'm also called a subway."}],"options":[{"label":"Tram","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Monorail","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Subway","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🌍"}}],"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Meow', and I like to chase string. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk."},{"text":"🧶 I love to play with yarn."},{"text":"🐈‍⬛ Some people keep me as a pet."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I bark and wag my tail. I love to play fetch! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I like to chew on bones."},{"text":"🎾 I'm a good friend and companion."},{"text":"🐕 I come in many different sizes and colors."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fish","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I quack and waddle. I swim in ponds and lakes. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌾 I like to eat seeds and plants."},{"text":"🐣 Baby version of me is called a duckling."},{"text":"🦆 I am a water bird."}],"options":[{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I hop and have long ears. I love to eat carrots! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I love to eat vegetables."},{"text":"🌱 I like to eat plants and leaves."},{"text":"🐇 Some people keep me as a pet, others live in wild."}],"options":[{"label":"Squirrel","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Mouse","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I roar and I am the king of the jungle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦁 I have a big mane."},{"text":"🥩 I am a carnivore."},{"text":"🌳 I live in Africa."}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. I never forget! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I love to eat peanuts."},{"text":"🌍 I live in Africa and Asia."},{"text":"🐘 I am a very big animal."}],"options":[{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Hippo","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I have black and white stripes, and I look like a horse. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦓 I live in Africa."},{"text":"🌿 I eat grass."},{"text":"🐎 My stripes are unique to each of us, like fingerprints."}],"options":[{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I hiss and slither. I don't have legs. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐍 I shed my skin."},{"text":"🥚 I lay eggs."},{"text":"🐁 Some of me eat mice."}],"options":[{"label":"Worm","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Snake","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Lizard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I have a pouch, and I hop around Australia. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🇦🇺 I am native to Australia."},{"text":"🌿 I eat plants and grasses."},{"text":"🦘 I carry my babies in a pouch."}],"options":[{"label":"Kangaroo","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Ostrich","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Llama","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I live in the ocean and have eight arms. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐙 I am an invertebrate."},{"text":"💦 I can squirt ink when I'm scared."},{"text":"🌊 I don't have any bones."}],"options":[{"label":"Starfish","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Octopus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Seahorse","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}]}